smoothjazz.com 2019-04-18

# Privacy Policy | SmoothJazz.com

### **SmoothJazz.com Privacy Policy**

Personally identifying information that you provide to the SmoothJazz.com of sites will not be made available to third parties outside of the SmoothJazz.com without your explicit permission.

The SmoothJazz.com collects personally identifying information about you only when you specifically and knowingly provide it to us. Your personally identifying information will be used to personalize your experience with the SmoothJazz.com Web sites, or for such other purposes as are described at any point where the SmoothJazz.com collects this information from you.

The SmoothJazz.com may make aggregate information about our customers (e.g. overall statistics) available to third parties for advertising and other purposes. Information that personally identifies you will be kept strictly confidential.

Personally identifying information which you choose to provide to another party or Web site will be subject to their privacy policy. For example, if you purchase goods or services online from a merchant you found while searching the SmoothJazz.com, information you provide to that merchant is subject to their privacy policy rather than ours.

###   
**Use of Cookies**

Cookies are pieces of information that a Web site transfers to an individual's hard disk for record-keeping purposes. Cookies can make the Web more useful by storing information about your preferences on a particular site, like what items you have in a "shopping cart" for an online store. The use of cookies is an industry standard, and many major Web sites use them to provide great features for their customers.

The SmoothJazz.com has two primary uses for its cookies. First, we use them to specify unique preferences. Secondly, we use cookies to track user trends and patterns. This helps us better understand and improve areas of the SmoothJazz.com service that our users find valuable. While both of these activities depend on the use of a "cookie," visitors to the SmoothJazz.com always have the option of disabling cookies via their browser preferences.

Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, note that some parts of the SmoothJazz.com service may not function properly if you refuse cookies.

###   
**Links to Sites**

Users should be aware that when you are on the SmoothJazz.com, you could be directed to other sites that are beyond our control. There are links to other sites from the SmoothJazz.com pages that take you outside our service. For example, if you "click" on a banner advertisement or a SmoothJazz.com search result, the "click" takes you off the SmoothJazz.com site. This includes links from advertisers, sponsors and partners that may use the SmoothJazz.com's logo as part of a co-branding agreement. These other sites may send their own cookies to users, collect data or solicit personal information. Always be aware of where you end up!

The SmoothJazz.com's policy does not extend to anything that is inherent in the operation of the Internet, and therefore beyond the SmoothJazz.com's control, and is not to be applied in any manner contrary to applicable law or governmental regulation.

###   
**Making Contact**

When you send us e-mail, we will use your name and e-mail address only to respond to the concerns you write to us with. Your e-mail may be shared with appropriate people within the SmoothJazz.com to help us respond to your concerns and improve the SmoothJazz.com.
